whoisology.com 2018-08-23

# Privacy policy - Whoisology

Last updated: May 15, 2018

This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Whoisology directly, it does not apply to the data within the Whois records displayed upon the Site.

**Personal identification information**

Users may also visit our Site anonymously.

We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily authorize submission of such information.

Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information. Please not that refusal to submit certain information may prevent the User from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and IP address the User uses to connect to our Site. Gathering this information can assist us with on our Site. Internet Service Providers typically use Dynamic IP addresses that change when you access different web sites as an added protection feature. Contact your Internet Service Provider to learn more about IP addresses, Dynamic IP addresses, and how they work to protect you and your use.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

Whoisology may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * **To improve customer service.** Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.

  * **To personalize user experience.** We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.  

  * **To improve our Site.** We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.  

  * **To process payments.** We may use the information. Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.  

  * **To run a promotion, contest, or survey.** We may use personal User information to send you material you have agreed to receive regarding topics we think will be of interest to you, this includes periodic emails. We may use the User’s email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. The User’s email address may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If the User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of **_each_** email, or the User may contact us via email.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt safe and applicable data collection, storage and processing practices, and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information, or data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**

We may share generic aggregated demographic information that is not personally identifiable and not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

We may share your information such as email address with these third parties for such limited purposes, provided that you have given us your express consent.

**Third party websites**

Browsing and interacting on any other website....

**Advertising**

These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non-personal identification information about you or others who use your computer.

This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Compliance with children's online privacy protection act**

Protecting the privacy of every youth is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information knowingly or willfully from anyone under the age or 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under the age of 13. Please note as mentioned above that our Site allows users to interact anonymously.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Whoisology has the discretion to update this Privacy Policy at any time.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed as your acceptance of those changes.
